http://www.rallyconnection.com/privacy/

+353(58)47000
+353(58)47000MENUMENUHomeAboutRally ExperiencesIntermediate Rally ExperienceAdvanced Rally ExperienceAdvanced Plus Rally ExperienceTailored Rally Driving PackagesJunior Rally Taster ExperienceStage Rallying Licence CourseGift VouchersCorporateStag & Hen PartiesVideosContactThis website is maintained by RallyConnection. RallyConnection fully respects your right to privacy, and will not collect any personal information about you on this website without your clear and explicit permission. Any personal information which you volunteer will be treated with the highest standards of security and confidentiality, strictly in accordance with the Data Protection Acts, 1988 and 2003.Collection and use of personal information
Any personal data which you provide to us using this website eg. Contact Form, Payment Form or Shopping Cart, will be used in line with the purposes for which you provided it. For example to reply to an enquiry which you have made through a contact form or to process payment for a product or service, which you have requested.Payment Information
We do not store any credit card information as part of any payment through this site. Your credit card details are simply passed securely to our payment processor (eg Paypal, Stripe or Realex) at the time you make your payment in order to gain authorisation from your bank.Information we routinely collect
We may collect the following information from each user of this site: Statistical information (IP address and hostname, web browser version, pages visited etc.) The previous website address from which you reached us, including any search terms usedWhat we use the information for
We will neither make attempts to identify individual visitors, nor associate the technical details listed above with any individual. It is our policy never to disclose such technical information in respect of individual website visitors to any third party unless explicitly stated, or obliged to disclose such information by a rule of law. The technical information will be used only for statistical and technical purposes.You should note that technical details, which we cannot associate with any identifiable individual, do not constitute ‘personal data’ for the purposes of the Data Protection Acts, 1988 and 2003.Cookies
Cookies are small pieces of information, stored in simple text files, placed on your computer by a website. Some cookies can be read by the website on your subsequent visits. The information stored in a cookie may relate to your browsing activities on the website, or a unique identifier so that the website can ‘remember’ you on your return visit. Other cookies are deleted when you close your browser and only relate to the working of the website. Generally speaking, cookies do not contain personal information from which you can be identified, unless you have furnished such information to the website.Cookies on this website
When you first visit this website, you will see a message informing you about cookies. If you click the ‘OK thanks’ button, a cookie will be set that records your preference. Most browsers allow you to turn off cookies or to customise your settings for cookies. To find out how to do this, see the ‘Help’ menu on your browser. Please note that if you turn off cookies or change your settings, some features of the website may not work correctly.Social Media Cookies
So you can easily “Like” or share our content using a variety of social media tools, we may include sharing buttons on some or all pages of our site. These buttons may include buttons from social media serivces such as Facebook, Twitter, LinkedIn and Google Plus etc. The privacy implications on this will vary from social network to social network and will be dependent on the privacy settings you have chosen on these networks, please refer to each individual site for their Privacy Policy.Google Analytics
We have introduced Google Analytics to assist us in the functioning of this website. This service helps us to provide relevant information in an easily accessible format.Glossary of technical terms used
Web Browser – The piece of software you use to read web pages. Examples are Microsoft Internet Explorer, Mozilla Firefox, Chrome and Opera.
IP Address – The identifying details for your computer (or your internet company’s computer), expressed in internet protocol code (for example 192.168.72.34). Every computer connected to the web has a unique IP address, although the address may not be the same every time a connection is made.Change of Privacy Statement
If our privacy policy changes, we will amend this website and privacy policy accordingly.Changes to Terms & Conditions
We reserve the right to update or modify these Terms and Conditions at any time without prior notice. For this reason, we encourage you to review these Terms and Conditions whenever you purchase products from us or use our website.Further information or to make a request
If you are concerned about how personal data is processed via this website, please do not hesitate to bring such concerns to our attention.Contact DetailsMobile: +353(86)2572302Landline: +353(58)47000Email: drive@rallyconnection.comRallyConnection
Millstreet, Cappagh,
Dungarvan,
Co. Waterford,
Ireland.Christmas Advert
Christmas Gift VouchersLooking for a Christmas gift for your friends/ colleagues or loved ones? RallyConnection offer the perfect Christmas gift ideas. more info
Buy NowRally ExperiencesIntermediate Rally ExperienceAdvanced Rally ExperienceAdvanced Plus Rally ExperienceTailored Rally Driving PackagesJunior Rally Taster ExperienceStage Rallying License CourseWhat others say!Cheers to Kevin for his great advice and bravery!! Also thanks to Tom for allowing me to roast that MK11.... moreChris MaguireRallyConnection Rally School
Whether you are a complete novice, intermediate or experienced driver, RallyConnection concentrates on improving your rallying skills in a friendly and professional atmosphere. No prior rally experience is required. All our instructors have a vast wealth of competitive rallying experience. They have competed at the highest level of rallying throughout Ireland and the UK.Providing rally driving experiences since 2003Rally ExperiencesIntermediate Rally ExperienceAdvanced Rally ExperienceAdvanced Plus Rally ExperienceTailored Rally Driving PackagesJunior Rally Taster ExperienceStage Rallying License CourseTerms & Conditions | Privacy StatementMobile: +353(86)2572302Phone: +353(58)47000Email: drive@rallyconnection.comRallyConnection
Millstreet, Cappagh,
Dungarvan,
Co. Waterford,
Ireland.
X35 KN76
Website by: Déise Design
